Guide to the Leonard S. Marcus Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2015 Acquisition, circa 1850-2015; circa 1975-2015; 110.08; (98 boxes)
  - Writings, circa 1981-2015; 77.5; (68 boxes)
    - Short Works, circa 1981-2015
      - Other Short Works and Events, circa 1981-2015
        - Marc Simont sketchbooks, Horn Book, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1324)
        - HarperCollins millennium project, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1325)
        - The New York Times Book Review best illustrated books, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1326)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Book Awards, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1327)
        - E. B. White letters, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1328-1329)
        - Connecticut Center for the Book awards, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1330)
        - Tomie dePaola Listening Library interview, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1331)
        - Interview with Cabinet Magazine, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1332)
        - Books for Kids Foundation, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1333)
        - Audiofile interview, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 1334)
        - Note for Valerie Lewis and Walter Mayes book, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1335)
        - University of Southern Mississippi conference anthology, circa 1995-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1336)
        - New School for Social Research conference, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 1337)
        - Connecticut Book Awards, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 1338)
        - Quote for Show and Tell by Dilys Evans, 2008 (Box 52, Folder 1339)
        - Riverbank Review interview, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 1340)
        - Kiriyama Pacific Rim Institute, circa 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1341)
        - Real Art Ways exhibition, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1342)
        - Listening Library interview with Paul Fleischman, circa 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1343)
        - Listening Library 45th anniversary history, circa 2000 (Box 52, Folder 1344)
        - Listening Library interview with Karen Hesse, circa 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1345)
        - Society of Illustrators original art show judging, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 1346)
        - Audie awards, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 1347-1348)
        - Horn Book Sendak issue essay, circa 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 1349)
        - Horn Book correspondence, circa 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 1350)
        - Walter Lorraine interview, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 1351)
        - Horn Book, 2001/2101 issue (Box 52, Folder 1352)
        - The Cambridge Guide to Children's Books, Ursula Nordstrom essay, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 1353)
        - Interview with Dorothy Briley, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1354)
        - Interview with Phyllis Fogelman, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1355)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Eric Carle gallery guide, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1356)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Crews and Jonas gallery guide, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1357)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Mary Azarian, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1358)
        - Five Owls New York article, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1359)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Peter Sís, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 1360)
        - A Little Princess introduction, Barnes and Noble edition, circa 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1361)
        - "How Goodnight Moon Became a Classic", 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1362)
        - Joie essay on Margaret Wise Brown, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1363)
        - Margaret Wise Brown article, Amazon.com, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1364)
        - Margaret Wise Brown cartoons, circa 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1365)
        - McElderberry book, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1366)
        - Margaret Wise Brown clippings and research, circa 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1367-1369)
        - Hollins College Summer Institute in Children's Literature lecture, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 1370)
        - Dana Hall School alumnae weekend, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1371)
        - The Wall Street Journal article, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1372)
        - Margaret Wise Brown speech at the Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 1373)
        - "Beyond the Great Green Room," Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 1374)
        - Coronado Library talk, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 1375)
        - Margaret Wise Brown correspondence, circa 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1376-1379)
        - Interesting clippings, circa 1999 (Box 53, Folder 1380)
        - Bank Street talk, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1381)
        - "Correspondence Course, or What I Learned from Editing Ursula Nordstrom's Letters," Texas Woman's University, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 1382)
        - Children's Literature New England talk, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 1383)
        - Reading Is Fundamental benefit talk, 2013 (Box 54, Folder 1384)
        - Harriet the Spy 50th Anniversary Edition event, 2014 (Box 54, Folder 1385)
        - "Once Upon a Nation: My Adventures in American Children's Book History," University of Maryland, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1386)
        - Maurice Sendak fellowship, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1387)
        - Kerlan Collection 60th anniversary, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1388)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Fred Marcellino exhibition, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1389)
        - Eric Carle Museum talk, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1390)
        - Lake County Discovery Museum exhibition, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1391)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1392)
        - BookExpo America, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1393)
        - Children's Literature Conference, University of Pittsburgh, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1394)
        - Jewish Museum talks, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1395)
        - Rey Center talk, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1396)
        - Georgetown Day School event, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1397)
        - Ezra Jack Keats talk, Jewish Museum, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1398)
        - National Louis University talk and slides, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1399)
        - Northport Public Library talk, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1400)
        - Queens Public Library event, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 1401)
        - Salt Lake City Public Library talk, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1402)
        - Bank Street Book Fest, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1403)
        - American Library Association preconference, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1404)
        - Eric Carle Museum event, 2010 (Box 54, Folder 1405)
        - William Paterson University program, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1406)
        - Iowa State Librarians Conference, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1407)
        - Baltimore CityLit Festival, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1408)
        - Joslyn Art Museum talks, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1409)
        - Midwest talks, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1410)
        - Children's Museum of Pittsburgh Fall Festival of Children's Books, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1411)
        - Kansas City interview and talk, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1412)
        - Texas Library Association, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 1413)
        - ICON Illustration Conference, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1414)
        - Conference of Teachers and Librarians keynote, Binghamton, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1415)
        - Hartford Public Library talk, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1416)
        - Princeton Public Library talk, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1417)
        - Brooklyn Historical Society, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1418)
        - Little Red School House talk, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 1419)
        - M. Jerry Weiss Center dinner, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1420)
        - Hollins walking tour, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 1421)
        - Nassau County Librarians walking tour, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 1422)
        - Winterthur Museum, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 1423)
        - Chicago Humanities Festival, 2008 (Box 54, Folder 1424)
        - Long Island Children's Museum Salty Stories reading list, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1425)
        - Disney Golden Books talks, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 1426)
        - American Library Association conference, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 1427)
        - "Children's Books and Editorial Vision," Texas Woman's University, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 1428)
        - New York City Department of Education, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 1429)
        - Charlotte S. Huck Children's Literature Festival, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 1430)
        - New York University Child Study Center, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 1431)
        - Kenosha Public Library talk, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 1432)
        - Cambridge Public Library talk, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 1433)
        - American Library Association midwinter meeting, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 1434)
        - Mock Caldecott, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 1435)
        - San Antonio and Brooklyn talks, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 1436)
        - History of children's nonfiction talk notes, circa 2007-2009 (Box 55, Folder 1437)
        - Margaret Wise Brown slide talk, circa 1981 (Box 55, Folder 1438)
        - Princeton University Cotsen Collection, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 1439)
        - Dear Genius talk material, circa 2000 (Box 55, Folder 1440)
        - Storied City talk material, circa 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 1441)
        - Storied City Yorkville talk material, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 1442)
        - Politics and Prose, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1443)
        - American Library Association conference, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1444)
        - Vermont College of Fine Arts, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1445)
        - Farnsworth Museum, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1446)
        - Boston Book Festival, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 1447)
        - Norman Rockwell Museum, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1448)
        - Shenandoah University, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1449)
        - BookExpo America, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1450)
        - Sharon Book Fair, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1451)
        - Politics and Prose, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1452)
        - Goshen Public Library, 2012 (Box 55, Folder 1453)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 1454)
        - Enoch Pratt Free Library, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 1455)
        - Teachers and Writers Collaborative interview, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1456)
        - Fort Lauderdale children's literature conference, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1457)
        - Phoenix Public Library, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 1458)
        - New York Public Library, Pforzheimer lecture, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 1459)
        - P. D. Eastman interview for the Loose Leaf Book Company, circa 2000-2003 (Box 55, Folder 1460)
        - 100 Dresses, circa 1999 (Box 55, Folder 1461)
        - Bologna Book Fair, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1462)
        - Princeton Library Book Festival, 2013 (Box 55, Folder 1463)
        - University of Connecticut and SUNY Albany, 2008-2013 (Box 55, Folder 1464)
        - Rhode Island School of Design Museum, 2009-2013 (Box 55, Folder 1465)
        - New York Public Library Children's Center talk, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1466)
        - Great Neck Public Library, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 1467)
        - Brooklyn Public Library, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 1468)
        - Newton Free Library, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 1469)
        - Southampton children's literature conference, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1470)
        - Lexington Public Library, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1471)
        - Williamsburg Regional Library, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 1472)
        - University of Central Arkansas, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 1473)
        - William Paterson University, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1474)
        - Little Shop of Stories, Decatur, Georgia, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1475)
        - Children's Literature Association conference, 2010 (Box 55, Folder 1476)
        - United Nations panel, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1477)
        - Jewish Museum Steig show program, 2008 (Box 55, Folder 1478)
        - Museum of Comic and Cartoon Art panel, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 1479)
        - American Library Association conference, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1480)
        - National Council of Teachers of English, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1481)
        - Texas events, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1482)
        - Children's Book Council book week breakfast, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 1483)
        - Long Island Children's Museum, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1484)
        - University of Buffalo talk, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 1485)
        - Bank Street Center for Children's Literature inaugural event, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1486)
        - American Library Association, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1487)
        - Rabbit Hill Festival, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1488)
        - Baltimore Book Festival, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1489)
        - BookExpo America, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1490)
        - Queens Public Library talk, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1491)
        - Hamptons Book Festival, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1492)
        - Brooklyn Public Library Reading Is Fundamental event, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1493)
        - University of Southern Mississippi, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 1494)
        - Brooklyn Public Library talk, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1495)
        - Zimmerli Arts Museum, 2007- (Box 56, Folder 1496)
        - Mazza summer institute, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1497)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators, Hofstra, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 1498)
        - Janet Hickmann tribute conference, Ohio State, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1499)
        - New York Psychoanalytic Institute, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1500)
        - Washington, D.C. museums, 2008 (Box 56, Folder 1501)
        - "Picture Book Animals: How Natural a History?", Social Values in Fantasy conference, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 1502)
        - Speech at Jacob Marcus's bar mitzvah, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1503)
        - Harris Symposium, Yale University, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 1504)
        - Barnes and Noble, Newburgh, New York, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1505)
        - Los Angeles Public Library, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1506)
        - Society of Illustrators, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1507)
        - Suffolk Children's Librarians walking tour, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1508)
        - Maple Hill Farm Festival, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1509)
        - Hudson Valley Writers' Center, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1510)
        - Rhode Island School of Design Museum, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1511)
        - Bank Street Reading Is Fundamental event, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1512)
        - Books of Wonder event, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1513)
        - Clinton Library, Alice Provensen Day presentation, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 1514)
        - Society of Illustrators, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1515)
        - American Library Association midwinter meeting, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 1516)
        - American Library Association conference, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1517)
        - American Library Association conference talk, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1518)
        - BookExpo America book signing and tour, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1519)
        - Billie Levy walking tour, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1520)
        - Reach Out and Read conference, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1521)
        - Los Angeles Public Library nonfiction talk, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1522)
        - Ohio State University, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 1523)
        - Eric Carle Museum, Bagels and Books talk, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 1524)
        - Good Morning America, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 1525)
        - Boston Globe and Horn Book award, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 1526)
        - New York Public Library talk for parents, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 1527)
        - Los Angeles Public Library, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1528)
        - Brooklyn Museum of Art, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1529)
        - New York Public Library talk, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 1530)
        - Ohio State University, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 1531)
        - SUNY Postdam talk, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1532)
        - Brooklyn Public Library talk, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1533)
        - BBC interview about Lemony Snicket, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1534)
        - Nassau County Library conference, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1535)
        - Rockland and Orange County Library program, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1536)
        - American Library Association preconference, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1537)
        - Brooklyn Public Library forum, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1538)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators website interview, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1539)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature opening, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 1540)
        - Verizon website interview, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 1541)
        - San Diego State University talk, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 1542)
        - Children's Literature Council of Southern California, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1543)
        - Whitney Museum of Art, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1544)
        - Rotunda Gallery lecture, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 1545)
        - The Century Committee on the Archives, circa 1995-2000 (Box 58, Folder 1553)
        - The New York Times Book Review, 2015 (Box 58, Folder 1554)
        - The Horn Book interview with Frances Foster, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 1555)
        - The Horn Book interview with George M. Nicholson, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 1556)
        - The Horn Book interview with Susan Hirshman, circa 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 1557-1558)
        - The Horn Book "Confounded Critic", circa 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 1559)
        - The Horn Book interview with Ethel Heins, circa 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 1560)
        - The Horn Book interview with Jean Feiwel, circa 2003-2007 (Box 58, Folder 1561)
        - Charlotte Zolotow lecture, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1562)
        - The Horn Book interview with Sheldon Fogelman, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 1563)
        - Nursery rhyme comics, circa 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1564)
        - Jerry Pinkney essay, Norman Rockwell Museum, 2010 (Box 58, Folder 1565)
        - School talk quotes, circa 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1566)
        - Abrams publicity, circa 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1567)
        - The New York Times Book Review, 3 nursery rhyme books, circa 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1568)
        - The New York Times Book Review, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1569)
        - Norton Juster award, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1570)
        - Madeleine L'Engle talk excerpts, circa 2010-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1571)
        - New England School Library Association, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1572)
        - Isol, Horn Book column, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1573)
        - New York Public Library exhibition article, Horn Book, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1574)
        - Racine Public Library, circa 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1575)
        - Singapore book chapter, circa 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1576)
        - New York Public Library, Marc Boutavant and Carin Berger, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1577)
        - Maurice Sendak talk, Bibliothèque nationale de France, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1578)
        - Maurice Sendak interview, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 1579)
        - Maurice Sendak catalog, circa 2011-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1580)
        - Maurice Sendak, Fine Books Magazine, circa 2011-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1581)
        - "Maurice Sendak: Storyteller and Psychologist," NYU Grand Rounds talk, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 1582)
        - Arbuthnot symposium, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 1583)
        - Maurice Sendak panel, Society of Illustrators, 2013 (Box 58, Folder 1584)
        - Maurice Sendak conference, Paris, circa 2011-2013 (Box 58, Folder 1585)
        - True Grit afterword, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 1586)
        - The Lion and the Unicorn, 1986–1989 (Box 59, Folder 1598)
        - The Lion and the Unicorn booklog, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1599-1600)
        - Parents' Choice Awards paperbacks, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 1601)
        - The Lion and the Unicorn booklog, circa 1985-1990 (Box 59, Folder 1606)
        - "New Heroes Before Their Time: A Talk on Some Recent American Picture Books," Frankfurt, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 1607)
        - Writing for Children workshop, San Francisco, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1608)
        - "Writing for Children," California College of Arts and Crafts, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1609)
        - Children's Books as Literature class, The New School for Social Research, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1610)
        - Children's Literature for Illustrators class, School of Visual Arts, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 1611)
        - Children's Books as Literature class, The New School for Social Research, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1612)
        - Talk on the history of children's magazines, American Library Association, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 1710)
        - The Complete Adventures of Curious George 60th anniversary edition introduction, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 1711)
        - Betsy Beinecke Shirley lecture, Yale University, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 1712)
        - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland art proofs, circa 1998 (Box 94 (Oversize), Folder 2310)
        - Mary Engelbreit's Nursery Tales black and white layout, 2007 (Box 96 (Oversize), Folder 2315)
  - Exhibitions and Museum Work, circa 1985-2013; 3; (3 boxes)
    Documents Marcus's work with museums, including exhibitions curated and service on boards of trustees and other advisory boards, particularly Marcus's service on the board of trustees of the Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art. Includes research materials, exhibition plans, correspondence, and docent training materials for exhibitions Marcus curated at the New York Public Library, Boston Athenaeum, and Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art, amongst others.
    Organized into four subseries: Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art Trusteeship; The ABC of It: Why Children's Books Matter, New York Public Library Exhibition; The Picture Book Made New: Margaret Wise Brown and Her Illustrators, Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art Exhibition; and Other Exhibitions and Museum Work.
    - Eric Carle Museum of Picture Book Art Trusteeship, circa 1998-2012
      - Eric Carle Museum building proposal, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 429)
      - Carle Honors, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 1613)
      - Upcoming exhibitions, circa 2002-2010 (Box 60, Folder 1614)
      - 5th anniversary exhibition with Katonah Museum of Art, circa 2007 (Box 60, Folder 1615-1618)
      - Children Should Be Seen: The Image of the Child in American Picture-Book Art exhibition catalog, circa 2007 (Box 60, Folder 1619-1622)
      - Growing Every Which Way But Up: The Children's Book Art of Jules Feiffer, circa 2011-2012 (Box 60, Folder 1623-1625)
      - Maurice Sendak: Inside Out exhibition catalog, circa 2002-2003 (Box 60, Folder 1626)
      - Carle Honors, 2006-2011 (Box 60, Folder 1627-1631)
      - Carle Museum General Awards, circa 2002-2011 (Box 60, Folder 1632)
    - The ABC of It: Why Children's Books Matter, New York Public Library Exhibition, circa 2011-2013
      - ABC of It Kiley, circa 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 430)
      - Picture key and checklist, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1633)
      - Research and correspondence, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1634-1636)
      - NYPL new research material, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1637-1638)
      - NYPL exhibition text, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1639)
      - NYPL object labels, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1640)
      - NYPL exhibition, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1641-1642)
      - The ABC of It research materials, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1643-1645)
      - The ABC of It docent training manual, circa 2013 (Box 61, Folder 1646)
      - The ABC of It Bank Street programs, circa 2013 (Box 61, Folder 1647)
      - NYPL event, 2013 (Box 61, Folder 1648)
      - Exhibition outline and plan, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1649-1650)
      - NYPL exhibition research material, circa 2011-2013 (Box 61, Folder 1651-1652)
      - The ABC of It press, 2013 (Box 61, Folder 1653-1654)
    - Other Exhibitions and Museum Work, circa 1985-2009
      - Mazza Museum national advisory board, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1546)
      - Steichen: Photographs for the Very Young exhibition, New York Public Library, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 1547)
      - Treasure Books: Selections from the Caroline M. Hewins Collection of Children's Literature exhibition, Hartford Public Library, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 1548)
      - The Picture Book Made New: Margaret Wise Brown and Her Illustrators exhibition, Eric Carle Museum, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 1549-1552)